{
    "id": "404900beef294613aae5fd7798134660",
    "title": "At, on and in exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fdad999f8afa46e2a9a99b721b658298",
            "title": "At, On And In",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We will come and see you …………………. Christmas day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It happened ……………….. the week before Christmas.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t seen him …………………… years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to see him ………………… lunchtime.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I first met her ………………….. a rainy morning in June.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Stanford is ……………………… the river Avon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren’t many apples ……………………… the tree this year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the good-looking girl ………………….. the sixth row?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "As there was no room …………………… the bus we got off.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is always ……………………… the hairdresser’s.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}